<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<DBIN2 xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" Key="1262735998" Unknown="1">
  <Entries>
    <Entry Unknown0="1505360020" Unknown1="93052752">
      <SDL2 Key="2881622554">
        <Unknown>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147456</Value0>
            <Value1>65536</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147458</Value0>
            <Value1>196608</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147460</Value0>
            <Value1>327680</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147462</Value0>
            <Value1>458752</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147464</Value0>
            <Value1>589824</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147466</Value0>
            <Value1>720896</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147468</Value0>
            <Value1>851968</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147470</Value0>
            <Value1>983040</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147472</Value0>
            <Value1>1114112</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147474</Value0>
            <Value1>1245184</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147476</Value0>
            <Value1>1376256</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147478</Value0>
            <Value1>1507328</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147480</Value0>
            <Value1>1638400</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147482</Value0>
            <Value1>1769472</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147484</Value0>
            <Value1>1900544</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147486</Value0>
            <Value1>2031616</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147488</Value0>
            <Value1>2162688</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147490</Value0>
            <Value1>2293760</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147492</Value0>
            <Value1>2424832</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147494</Value0>
            <Value1>2555904</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147496</Value0>
            <Value1>2686976</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147498</Value0>
            <Value1>2818048</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147500</Value0>
            <Value1>2949120</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147502</Value0>
            <Value1>3080192</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147504</Value0>
            <Value1>3211264</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147506</Value0>
            <Value1>3342336</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147508</Value0>
            <Value1>3473408</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147510</Value0>
            <Value1>3604480</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147512</Value0>
            <Value1>3735552</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147514</Value0>
            <Value1>3866624</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147516</Value0>
            <Value1>3997696</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147518</Value0>
            <Value1>4128768</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147520</Value0>
            <Value1>4259840</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147522</Value0>
            <Value1>4390912</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147524</Value0>
            <Value1>4521984</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147526</Value0>
            <Value1>4653056</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147528</Value0>
            <Value1>4784128</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147530</Value0>
            <Value1>4915200</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147532</Value0>
            <Value1>5046272</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147534</Value0>
            <Value1>5177344</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147536</Value0>
            <Value1>5308416</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147538</Value0>
            <Value1>5439488</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147540</Value0>
            <Value1>5570560</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147542</Value0>
            <Value1>5701632</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147544</Value0>
            <Value1>5832704</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147546</Value0>
            <Value1>5963776</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147548</Value0>
            <Value1>6094848</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147550</Value0>
            <Value1>6225920</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147552</Value0>
            <Value1>6356992</Value1>
          </Entry>
          <Entry>
            <Values />
            <Value0>147554</Value0>
            <Value1>6488064</Value1>
          </Entry>
        </Unknown>
        <Dialogs>
          <Dialog>Fountain Park</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Fountain Park is located not far from Shin-Towa Station. It is a popular spot for the citizens of Chiba to relax and enjoy cherry blossoms in the spring and ginkgo trees in the fall, showing their seasonal faces. The park is crowded with citizens all year round, both on weekdays and holidays.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Little Park</Dialog>
          <Dialog>With only a few pieces of playground equipment and an open space, the park has no particular name. However, citizens affectionately call it a "little park" and it always ranks high in surveys of favorite spots. It's a hidden and popular spot to enter.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Shin-Towa Station</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Shin-Towa Station is the nearest station to the school for students of Towano High School. The area around the station is crowded with students. The area between Shin-Towa station and Towano station is the main street in the city, and is lined with electric shops and entertainment facilities. I am.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Dixies</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Dixie's is a family restaurant that operates as a chain in and around the city of Towano. It has been a favorite of the citizens of Towano for its sweets. Recently, a rival restaurant has been in the news for expanding into the neighborhood.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Touji Temple</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Touji Temple is a famous temple with its head temple in Okujuano, which has been in existence for over 400 years. Since it is more convenient to get to the temple than the main temple, many people from inside and outside of the city visit the temple throughout the year. It is crowded with worshippers.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Western-Style House</Dialog>
          <Dialog>It's an old Western-style building that has attracted many people's attention for its opulent construction, but it's not known who lived there and what the purpose of the building was, and recently there have been rumors about the legend of Dracula.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Towano Station</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Looking at the size of the station, the number of passengers per day, and the bustle of the surrounding area, this is the main terminal of the city of Towa. It would not be an exaggeration to say that the city is located in the center of the city and is a gateway for citizens who are traveling far from home. It is located in the heart of the city and is a gateway for citizens who are traveling far from home.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>game centre</Dialog>
          <Dialog>It is a popular amusement facility with the latest game enclosures and a large selection of large medal machines. We have not only newer games, but also retro games, which are popular among retro game fans. There seems to be.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>electrical district</Dialog>
          <Dialog>The main street between Shin-Towano Station and Juhano Station, on the Juhano side of the main street, used to be an electronics street with many electronics shops lining the streets, but now it has become a major entertainment district with game shops and animation shops.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Shiobano Castle</Dialog>
          <Dialog>The historic ruins of Juhano Castle used to be just the outer moat and the stone walls, but now the castle tower has been restored, and there is no longer any room for a new castle tower. It has become a popular spot for visitors from inside and outside the city. It is.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>television station</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Towa TV has an established reputation for creating bold programs that are local while remaining close to the community. This is a local TV station. The production staff's strong love for the city of Towa is evident in their programs.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Tower Hilltop Station</Dialog>
          <Dialog>The area of Towa-no-Sakaue has developed as a suburban bedroom community in Towa City, which has been undergoing redevelopment in recent years. It is There is an abundance of large entertainment and cultural facilities, including an amusement park, botanical gardens and indoor pool facilities.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>amusement park</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Spark World has always been a popular spot as the only amusement park in the city of Towa. The symbol of Spark World is the large Ferris wheel, which offers a magnificent view of the city of Towa. It seems to be a regular date course.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>indoor swimming pool</Dialog>
          <Dialog>This is a large heated swimming pool facility that can be enjoyed in swimsuits all year round. Not only can you enjoy the flowing pools and water slides, but you can also enjoy refreshments here. It has become a popular classic spot for couples.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>river terrace</Dialog>
          <Dialog>The Juhano River is a symbol of the eastern part of the city. The riverbed is well maintained and its promenade and banks are popular as a running course. The sunset that can be seen from the bank of the Juhano River is reputed to be beautiful.  </Dialog>
          <Dialog>seaside station</Dialog>
          <Dialog>The area around the Rinkai Station is one of the fastest growing areas in the recent redevelopment of the city of Towa. Large commercial and entertainment facilities have been built in this area, making good use of the large space that was originally available, making it a popular place for young people. Commercial District.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>event hall</Dialog>
          <Dialog>This multipurpose complex is located near Rinkai Station. A park, a large and small hall, and a medium-sized stadium are all concentrated in this complex, and each facility offers a variety of live performances and exhibitions. Meetings and other events are held daily.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>mole</Dialog>
          <Dialog>It is a large commercial facility that represents the commercial district of Rinkai Station and is home to a large number of fashion and general merchandise stores. Shops have entered the store. This is a popular spot for young people, and it's packed with people every day.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Sky Tower</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Sky Tower is one of the most popular sightseeing spots in the coastal area, along with the Bay Bridge and Harbor Hill Park. . It is also a large lighthouse and is still in use.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Harbor Hill Park</Dialog>
          <Dialog>The park is located on top of a hill from which you can see the port, Sky Tower, the seaside area, and the coastal area.  The park is one of the most popular parks in the city of Towa, which is home to many lush greenery-rich parks, perhaps because of its spectacular scenery.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Bay Bridge</Dialog>
          <Dialog>The Bay Bridge is popular not only with residents of the city, but also with tourists who drive from outside the city to visit Towa City.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>aquarium</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Located between the harbor side and the coast side of the Rinkai district, the Aquarium of Towa is a popular spot that attracts many visitors from inside and outside the city as it exhibits rare deep-sea fish such as honey bream sharks and other live fish.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Sea Bathing</Dialog>
          <Dialog>The beaches in Towa City have less garbage and better water quality and sand, so a lot of people come to the beach during the swimming season. This is the spot where beachgoers visit. The seasonal Umi no Ie is also a hidden gourmet spot.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Chinese restaurant</Dialog>
          <Dialog>There are a lot of Chinese restaurants around Rinkai Station, but this one, despite being a chain, is still a good place to eat. This is a restaurant with a reputation for its high quality of taste. They are considering opening more shops in the city of Towa.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Fish Market</Dialog>
          <Dialog>The fish market supports the kitchen of Towa City. Originally centered around this port area, it has become a commercial district and a popular area for young people. However, the fish market is still vibrant and full of fresh discoveries to be made.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>boat embarkation area</Dialog>
          <Dialog>A number of ships, including cruise ships, commercial and fishing vessels, dock here. Recently, the Gulf Coast Cruise from here has been secretly attracting attention as a service that offers an extraordinary experience. It seems to be gaining in popularity.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Okubano Station</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Further north from the top of the hill in Towa, you will reach Okujuhano, a secluded area in Towa City. This is a land with a long history of mountain beliefs, and there are many tourist spots such as museums, a zoo, and ski resorts. There are a number of them.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>lake</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Lake Juhano is famous for its clarity, and its swan-shaped boats are popular. Forget the hustle and bustle of the city and enjoy a relaxing time in the suburbs. Recently, sightings of unidentified animals have become the talk of the town.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Mountain Top Art Museum</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Juwano Museum of Art is a place where you can enjoy first-class art in the nature of Oku Juwano. Despite being located in the suburbs, the museum is a popular spot for visitors of all ages.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Mountain Top Zoo</Dialog>
          <Dialog>The "Towa Zoo" is a popular zoo that incorporates behavioral exhibits and is crowded with visitors from inside and outside the city. The service to hold the baby animals is also very popular and there are long lines in front of the service. The service for holding baby animals is also very popular, and there is a long line of people waiting in front of the service.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Mt. Tenwa</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Mt. Amaosan, the symbol of Juhano City. According to legend, the name "Juhano" comes from the shape of its peaks, which look like ten wings spread. In recent years, it has gained a reputation as a popular vacation spot where visitors can enjoy nature in a casual manner.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>plateau</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Perhaps in response to the recent eco-consciousness, the Okujubano plateau area is a hot spot in recent years. There are wetlands with rare highland plants, ranches and farms, and the area has been attracting attention as an eco-friendly tourist spot. I'm bathed in it.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Okubano Onsen</Dialog>
          <Dialog>In recent years, Oujuano has become very popular as a tourist destination, and this is part of the reason for its popularity The first of these is Okujubano Onsen. The quality of the hot spring water is good, and the taste of the rustic hot spring town may be the secret of its popularity.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>waterfall</Dialog>
          <Dialog>The charm of Okujubano is that it is close to the city and you can enjoy nature easily. This famous waterfall, called "Kegon of Okujuwano", has been visited by many tourists in recent years.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Shiobano High School</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Private Juhano High School has a long history, but its free school culture is appealing, and many people from inside and outside the city are interested in entering the school. The students come together every year. There are many events throughout the year, and students seem to actively participate in them.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>library</Dialog>
          <Dialog>The library at Juhano High School is famous for its rich and varied collection of books. Recently, a female library staff member with uncommonly good looks, but who is very strict with the users, has been working in the library. It seems to be a rumor on campus.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>tennis court</Dialog>
          <Dialog>The Juwano High School Tennis Club is as free as the school culture. With the goal of deepening friendships through tennis, the club occasionally holds mixed-gender doubles friendly matches, and many It seems to be well received by the members of the department of</Dialog>
          <Dialog>back of the school building</Dialog>
          <Dialog>The back of the school building at Juwano High School is nondescript and empty. However, there is a common belief among the students that "if you confess your love to the person you love in the back of the school building, it will go well." There seems to be a rumor that has been passed down for a long time.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>courtyard</Dialog>
          <Dialog>The courtyard of Juhano High School is a well-kept garden with a central object in the center.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Ground</Dialog>
          <Dialog>The Sports Festival in September is one of the biggest events of the whole school, and many students are looking forward to it. There are a variety of events. There are a variety of events, and even though it is a high school sports festival, there is a scavenger hunt.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>swimming pool</Dialog>
          <Dialog>The pool at Juwano High School is a very standard 25-meter long, six-course pool. The opening of the pool in July every year is highly anticipated by the male students, although there is no unusual event. It seems to be a hidden and popular event.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>rooftop</Dialog>
          <Dialog>There are no tall buildings around the school, and the school itself is located on a gentle hill, so you can see as far as the bay area from the rooftop, which is popular with students for its hidden, spectacular view.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>school cafeteria</Dialog>
          <Dialog>The cafeteria at Juhano High School has been well received by both students and teachers for the variety of menu items and good taste! . However, the price per dish is no different from a normal restaurant, even though it is a school cafeteria.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>school store</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Like the school cafeteria, the purchasing department at Juhano High School has a large selection of items, even those that are obviously not related to schoolwork, and sometimes they even carry rare items that are only available here.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Towanohigashi Station</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Towanohigashi Station is the gateway to the hot new area "Towanohigashi". It has the serenity of the Juhano River and its banks, as well as many art facilities and specialty shops. It's an area that has both.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>shopping street</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Unlike the shopping malls in the seaside district, many specialty shops are located in the East of Towanohigashi shopping district. This is a very special place. The specialty shop area attracts many and diverse enthusiasts from inside and outside the city.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>camera shop</Dialog>
          <Dialog>One of the specialty shops in the shopping district is this camera shop. They carry a large number of camera parts, and sometimes they bring in rare and rare items that are not even sold in large stores. There seems to be.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>gallery</Dialog>
          <Dialog>Another feature of the East Towanohigashi area is that visitors can experience the latest art scene. In particular, the seasonal photography exhibitions, which display masterpieces submitted from all over the country, attract many visitors. It's a busy place.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>place to eat</Dialog>
          <Dialog>After visiting the specialty shops and enjoying the art scene, you can relax and enjoy a meal. This is the charm of East Towanohigashi. Although it is a small area, there are many restaurants competing with each other.</Dialog>
          <Dialog>House of Cooking Utensils</Dialog>
          <Dialog>One of the more unusual specialty shops is this cookware store. Recently, the number of couples visiting this restaurant seems to be increasing, and it seems that home-cooked food is becoming more popular in Towa City. Some experts seem to think that this is not the case.</Dialog>
        </Dialogs>
      </SDL2>
    </Entry>
  </Entries>
</DBIN2>